Your Majesty, please wait a moment.
Prince Yu may be delayed by something.
Didn't he write to say
he would visit the Imperial Consort Dowager
at Lingguo Temple before coming to the palace?
He's too arrogant.
After returning to the capital,
he didn't even come to see me first.
[Here comes His Highness Prince Yu.]
Your Majesty,
Prince Yu has arrived.
I, Mu Yunzheng,
pay my respects to Your Majesty.
You have been away from the capital for years.
You must have forgotten the palace rules.
Entering the palace with weapons
is a serious breach of protocol.
This sword
is a gift to Your Majesty.
It's made from the skull of an enemy leader.
May our empire
be invincible.
Prince Yu,
you're so kind.
After visiting my mother this morning,
I hurried to the palace.
But unexpectedly,
I was stopped by a commoner halfway.
So I was late.
I hope Your Majesty will punish me.
Your reputation as the Cold-faced General
has spread all over Kyoto.
Who dares to stop your way?
That woman held a bloody letter,
claiming to seek justice for her father.
I thought she was a rascal,
so I drove her away.
But just now,
I learned that
that woman
is actually Princess Consort of Rui.
I also heard that
she has been beating the Petition Drum
for several days.
Your Majesty,
I don't know about it.
All right.
We'll talk about it later.
Prince Yu,
please sit down.
You have been away from the capital for eight years.
Do you know why you are suddenly summoned back?
Wasn't it said that my mother was seriously ill?
I went to see her this morning.
I found she just caught a cold.
It's not as serious as the letter said.
Her illness is just an excuse.
I have another reason to call you back.
We were defeated by the Western Shu.
Soon,
they sent a letter of accusation.
They want to form an alliance with us.
They also said that the princess
wants to marry you.
I do have some relationship
with the princess of Western Shu,
but I have no intention of marrying her.
I just want to guard the border
for Your Majesty and the Great Wei.
I know you are loyal to the Great Wei
without any doubt.
Therefore,
when I knew
Xiao Wei committed treason,
although I know your relationship with him,
I never doubted you for a moment.
After all, you are my brother,
and would never do anything to harm the empire.
Your Majesty,
I also don't know
why General Xiao would take such a rebellious action.
Xiao Wei and Shen Yi are guilty of treason,
although the evidence is solid,
there are still many speculations about this case.
Looking at the imperial court,
there is no suitable candidate to take over this case.
Why don't you take it over?
With Hao'er's assistance, of course.
Please forgive me.
I've been leading troops at the border for years.
I've never been involved in court affairs,
nor do I know how to investigate cases.
Please withdraw the order.
About this,
don't rush to refuse.
I'll think about it.
Uncle.
Uncle, please wait.
You just returned to Kyoto to take over such an important case.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
Who are you?
I apologize for my lack of manners.
I am Prince Jing Zhao.
Zhao'er.
When I was in the capital,
I had some impression of you.
You've grown up a lot.
But you don't have to worry.
I won't take over this case.
Goodbye.
Your Highness, you'll have to make do for a few days.
The mansion's been unused for years.
Renovating the yard alone took several days.
Your Highness,
there are still several places that need renovation.
It doesn't matter.
I live alone anyway.
Don't bother too much.
By the way,
prepare another guest room.
Prince, do you have a guest?
Is it for Shen Suhe?
You are
getting more and more unruly.
By the way,
I still have a question.
Since His Majesty has agreed to re-examine the case,
why do you still refuse?
After all,
there are less than half a month
before Minister Shen's execution.
Now is not the time to take over the case.
If we are not careful,
we will not only fail to overturn the case,
but also get ourselves into trouble.
By the way,
what has Shen Suhe done
during my absence?
Did she come to see me?
You left without saying goodbye
and didn't leave any message.
She can't find you even if she wants to.
But
the secret guard guarding the Imperial Consort Dowager said
that Miss Shen found the Imperial Consort Dowager
by some means.
The Imperial Consort Dowager asked her to hide in the room
and let the guard protect her.
She went to see the Imperial Consort Dowager?
When I visited the Queen Mother this morning,
she didn't mention this at all.
Did they really know each other?
Anything else?
Yes.
Miss Shen and her maid
sneaked out of Lingguo Temple several times
and went to the Prime Minister's Residence.
They should be looking for evidence.
During this period, the Second Prince's pursuers
were intercepted by us.
Did they mention what they were looking for?
No.
Shen Suhe
Your Highness
A woman is waiting outside to see you.
I...
We just moved in today,
and someone came to visit.
Do you know who she is?
The woman didn't tell her identity,
but she's been kneeling outside,
She said if she couldn't see you,
she would keep kneeling.
Shen Suhe.
She came so soon.
Send her away.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
With her personality,
she won't leave.
We can't
let her keep kneeling there.
Then take her away.
Your Highness, are you willing to see me?
Miss,
His Highness has ordered that
he won't see any guests today.
Please go at your leisure.
I, Shen Suhe,
implore Your Highness to uphold justice
and clear the names of the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
I, Shen Suhe,
implore Your Highness to uphold justice
for the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
I, Shen Suhe,
seek justice from Your Highness
for the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
I, Shen Suhe,
seek justice from Your Highness
for the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
Your Highness,
are you going to let her keep this up?
Your reputation in Kyoto is already bad.
If she keeps this up,
I'm afraid
no one will dare to
step into the Yu Prince's Mansion.
Your Highness, please do justice.
Isn't that better?
I can have a peace of mind.
I, Shen Suhe,
seek justice from Your Highness.
Please clear the names of the PM and General Xiao.
Shen Suhe, what a troublemaker!
She shouldn't have
provoked the Emperor's uncle.
Your Highness.
Fifteenth,
do you think my father has suspected me
for asking the Emperor's uncle to take over the case?
Your Highness,
in my opinion,
His Majesty didn't suspect you,
but to test Prince Yu.
Think about it,
Prince Yu has been at the border for eight years.
Now that he has suddenly returned to the capital,
Your Majesty naturally wants to test his loyalty.
What you said makes some sense.
But even so,
my uncle is a very strange person.
If he really takes over this case,
I'm afraid he'll eventually find out about me.
Your Highness,
do you remember
the novel about the princess consort
and Prince Yu that was popular in the city?
Regardless of the authenticity of the novel,
there's no smoke without fire.
If His Majesty knows
that Prince Yu and Shen Residence are involved,
do you think
he will hand over the case to him?
Fifteenth,
I'll leave this to you.
Yes.
Uncle,
I didn't mean to offend you.
But I have no other way.
Your Highness,
I beg you to uphold justice
and clear the names
of the Prime Minister and General Xiao.
Your Highness, you are really prescient.
The Second Prince has been spreading
rumors about you and the Prime Minister's Residence.
Fortunately, you returned to the capital
and did not take over the case.
However,
Shen Suhe has been kneeling here for so long.
I'm afraid she can't hold on
before the Prime Minister.
I beg Your Highness to uphold justice
and clear the Prime Minister's...
Go back.
and General Xiao's innocence.
Please help us
clear the names
of the PM and General Xiao.
Your Highness,
it's a scorching day.
Have some tea
to avoid heatstroke.
Take this pot of tea away.
To whom?
Well.
I'm Shen Suhe.
I want to see Prince Yu.
He's worried you might die here,
so he asked me to bring you tea.
It's you.
Can I see him now?
You'd better leave.
He won't see you for a while.
What do you mean?
Does he
not want to see me now?
It's no use dragging me.
It's the prince who doesn't want to see you.
Do you know
where Master Lou went?
Master Lou?
You mean him?
He
was sent by the prince to deal with other affairs.
When will he come back?
It may take a few months
or years.
I don't know the details.
Where was he sent to?
How can I get in touch with him?
If he wants to see you,
he will come to you.
If not,
you can't get in touch with him.
I advise you
to forget him as soon as possible.
Forget?
How can I forget him so easily?
I, Shen Suhe,
implore you to seek justice
and clear the names of the PM and General Xiao.
Rui'er,
how long has His Highness not been here?
Maybe three or five days.
It seems that since Prince Yu returned,
His Highness has never been here.
By the way,
I also heard that
Shen Suhe knelt at the gate of Prince Yu's Mansion every day.
Shen Suhe again?
What does she want to do with my uncle?
For what else?
She just wants Prince Yu to help her save her father.
It's a pity that she can't even get in the mansion.
Let alone to see Prince Yu.
No wonder His Highness stays in the study all day.
He's afraid that my uncle will interfere in the case.
I can't let that bitch continue to make trouble.
Your Highness,
it's raining cats and dogs.
She's still kneeling outside.
Isn't this Miss Shen of the Prime Minister's Residence?
How did Miss Shen get like this?
At this time,
who are you still putting on airs for?
From Lingguo Temple to Prince Yu's Mansion,
haven't you been humiliated enough?
What are you pretending?
What?
Your Highness has found a new lover?
You have time to come here to bother me.
Shut up.
Your act
is really clumsy.
Shen Suhe,
don't be so complacent.
Even if you kneel here to death,
the Emperor Uncle will not care about you.
Your father
is beyond help.
Ling Chuchu,
if I were you,
I would have thought about my own way out.
You still have the leisure
to come here and insult me.
What do you mean?
Now my father has been imprisoned,
and I have been expelled from the mansion.
But Prince Rui
has never asked His Majesty
to divorce me.
Do you really think
he only loves you?
What are you talking about?
He promised me
that after your father is beheaded,
he will make me the principal wife.
Principal wife?
You are too naive.
If I can save my father,
I will be the only principal consort
of Prince Rui's Mansion.
If I don't save my father,
the Second Prince will have no opponent
in the imperial court.
He
will be the only candidate for the Crown Prince.
At that time, many noble families
will want to marry their daughters to him.
Do you really think you can keep
his heart for a lifetime?
Shut up!
Shen Suhe,
stop pretending!
Get up!
Still pretending?
I... I...
I can't breathe.
Who dares to be so rude in front of my mansion?
Your Highness,
I'm the secondary consort of the Second Prince.
I... I didn't mean it.
You rascal!
You not only hurt people without reason,
but also cling to the royal family.
Guards!
Take her to the court to be punished.
I'm the beloved concubine of the Second Prince.
How dare you!
You...
You let me go!
Don't you want to see me?
Stop pretending.
Your Highness,
I had to do this.
Your Highness.
Shen Suhe, Shen Suhe.
Your Highness,
I just wanted to help you deal with Shen Suhe
and drive her away from your mansion.
So you sent her to my mansion.
I...
I didn't expect that.
Shen Suhe is really cunning.
But Your Highness,
in this way,
the rumors all over the city will be confirmed.
The uncle and the princess consort...
Shut up.
You don't want those rumors to come true, do you?
You're starting to care about Shen Suhe, aren't you?
What do you know?
What I want is for my uncle not to interfere,
and Shen Yi not to rise again.
You sent Shen Suhe in.
How stupid you are!
Then why don't you report him?
Report him for having an affair with Shen Suhe.
I'll see how he can continue the trial.
That's right.
But what I want to report is
that he used public power for private gain,
colluded with the PM's Residence,
and was a traitor with Shen Yi.
My father has always been wary of him.
Maybe
what I did just meets his wishes.